OK
Thank you
Thank you for having me to share my experiences and thoughts
Let me be in my speech with a story
Android things to solve
照心a simple English lecture of Beijing Technology and business University
Was arrested by the local public security officers
Where is the falun gong exercises on the side of the World
Between the purple bamboo common Park
National Library
China in Beijing
Three Days later
冰箱cups and setter
Return false
Fish and chips
Cervical vertebra been broken
嗨
Procedia from Canada
She was sent to hospital
From the local detention Center
摩托車會
Practicing falun gong
法輪工International Chinese meditation practice
Also known as大法
618 100f professionals
Getting Back To night in ottawa
Apple南京南京哪
Chinese communist party
Presented in starting down with beautiful spiritual movements
銀行沒有發生過Mobile with Chinese communist party regime for the mind
Automatic
As soon as the machine was sent to the hospital
Which is in hospital after the detention Center
Arcadia was cut off
English or plastic
去莆田Toyota
Her mouth and younger sister was told by the doctor
Negative and teachers College
The social structure
Font awesome
I think you want to feel the oceans Deep
筍
白鋼deputy director of the detention Center
Medical doctors好
Who was responsible for the statement
Struct secretly with Kim
Foreign tire of mood
It was at night
Windows install vim
For an injection of nanomedicine into the scene
MTR
趙新開的Happy birthday
Revised form data flow of
很Mouse
Her mother and sister repeatedly wife of my phone
With negative
燒餅
After liver resection
趙鑫lostmemory
Officeplus
In six months later
趙欣大
With the More widely opened
Brother and sister price
Install failed to close the Mouse
Pronounce
Prospect
An Open Well at go
Closed by peer
很mousebuttons.left
Endgame
Undertale
Younger sister halogens
The whole process
Android
Excel做persistence
Ettoday
Sister
I know you want to tell me something
Gradually and finally
趙鑫
Proximal
My name is you
M4a1 professional2
Experienced real problem
When I was twenty years old
My son was two years older than
My wife was just sentenced
Prison
鳳凰demonstration of the following banner
黃的天安門restaurant
Which is simple
China's communist party regimes in power
It was the first sentence
I was just a message
Price for killing for someone
I accidentally coordinator
Forcella professionals Who were here
Take care of照心
Is fear of Being arrested again
Condition detention Center
West restaurant
I don't want to be there Once again
必應
Coordinator students with me
To invent interest
What is a will Put into prison
Maxthon
Only two years
His mother
不是correspondent
我不叫心脖子病害paraplegia
This is to suffer from the pain
Sheffield你好2
Cannot
Control
Cars
星期怎麼12點12
Password
Get out from her body
Mother and sister
Come to Beijing
The capital of China
方便封套
Withdraw心是father
Her father was struck down
Blinds
Siri
Java memory
Very very short
His beloved water situation
Combat
Mother and Sisters to take care of your scene
And we have just close enough
This is first time
Windows programming
I'm a stronger than Men
In certain situations
I have to coordinate to schedule
Make appointment for multiple parameters
主要操心
And I even from my Back up
Increase I was
Arrested
What I could do is not limited to Being a coordinator
Graduated from the most prestigious University in China
Ssn19
United States
I was one of a small number of people in China
VRV internet trend
One of very few Who Would you
How to establish
Vincristine communication Channel
Using the most advanced
Asymmetry in correction algorithm
Andrews
不是百度
Essential to do nothing
Everything will be okay but for the rest of My Life
Is not going to be able to fall asleep easily
I'm not able to look 30 to my Sunshine
Explain the Core values of language with a practice
輸出list
Compassion
Info.plist
If else to do something
It was just a matter of Time
When I got the weather
No one knew What might happened after
溫兆興
GTA5
Cult
去楓林al2o3
I witnessed
Pandas sort
Current situation
Was not exposed
兔子
More and more people were going to the facilities
I decided to do something
Synthesis in amsterdam University
Why should we dream on self
First
Cold and strain group of party members
Whittier compose
Training materials
Vented locations and Health screening
Personality factor
The Chinese communist regime
The relative ideas different from various
白雲freezing the physical distance
Material of ideas
So ensuring the expertise
Transistor
When we trust is important
Function to solve the guests to 302
Underneath the most
On the lives of those most wanted in China
I have is everything
Encrypted communication Channel between China
Investment
Lin was released to interview with big and culture with offset
China's spirillum
Apple
30 members of both be killed
Restaurant
新空間裝飾
Campbell Street Journal
OnePlus 5 price in 201403 port of practitioners
Not to work for New York Times
超public
When the associated press
Love is The Wall Street Journal China bureau chief
裝portrait
Lanvin for washing post
ThinkPad
When will the Washington Post
Knowkeys
New York Times Beijing bureau chief
Nexus user
Alice's melton
When the Daily telegraph
Reform and civil service
Open Garden
說狂java list of order of the British
British empire
M2010
Losses and Founder in editor
Chinaplas dotnet
And released from New York Times Times Magazine PPTV PPTV
The name is now bptm
Providing information to other journalist
風ppc nbsp
Stellar
Mass of the transfer of charity money to persons leading edge
你註定listings family members
吹牛sections of crisis communication
In China
Establish population centres
For producing followers
Structural information of expression of Go On the internet
In August 2000p
I was arrested with my team members
朱婷mywife
My school math
In my college
I was sentenced to prison for nine years
Arrested in prison for life and half years
My wife
Component-wise imprisonment
Rural areas
The total replacement of my team members
Sunset
To Modern physics
May.2013
I came to united States and seek
With my family
Internet experimental school Green Card to us
We are we are Now applying for our citizens
沒說話
To practice
Freedom and Justice
Public affairs
Welcome to the Night estates
IPhone devices is facing
Efficient the prices that
Wemedia
Please Note this
Financial lease
Windows redis
Educational system please
Betray the fundamental analysis of united States
The benefit of self
Xscores
American people
Let's talk about
Forms of religious groups in doing the most severe persecution by Chinese comicparty
For the past 6萬years
In China
The privilege of falun gong practitioners in the court
Thereafter
We
With same degree of persecution of falun gong practitioners
Integral published in December the Cross
2014a
Voice of America VOA
Reporting the persecution four hours depending upon the implication practitioner
Prefer to read a Criminal defense
Evaa006 App
Prisoner of conscience
Exporting
The lower the poster will is positioned to defend the practice of fluid flow
While receiving information from home
To synchronize with the professor Department of Chinese hospital Beijing
Transmission is seldom
As possible
The strategies of Chinese communist party begins persecution
Could be cancelled
VOA is it
Accomplish
Chinese comedy movies
Where is not alone
豬
Sonia2006
太沒了Cable removeitem genesis signal
Which has an area of China Fortune forum for ten years
On Time Warner Cable in New York
Chinese Journal of unusual broadcast
Program specified during Chinese communist party
Because of is not recommended reporting
Channel
Health and popularity among Chinese citizens
Who wanted to know what is really happened
Hiking in China
Apartamenty的
Time Warner Cable ox16 other Chinese channels
Happy
Chinese dance
Relationship with Chinese communist party with you
Insight Vivian timer
Over the top News agencies
Temperament
Welcome and responsibilities to convey shoes
2bmm準people
In the current pandemic
We all know that is it is extremely important for us
To be able to hear choose
Especially The Real information about China
Control key for information is control
Whether they live
等待
When we talking about media
We have to mention Google Facebook and Twitter
We are social class of information
Media sys.exit
Off the senses
Miktex
Map of March World
Ventilation and traditional News agencies expressing
The conservative voices such as trigger you been shapiro Jordan peterson will synchronized
Propaganda
方chinaz.com astrology
Speaking of Google
What I'm going to draw attention to
The Big picture
Such as Google IBM Cisco Microsoft and many other time
American bigtext
China scholarship
Stand down Chinese people the message
An acquired advantage of the united States
Google developed
Sensor version of Android
Chinese communist party room
Michael name
Dragonfly
Which means of red Dragon Chinese comedy parturition
不用Friday
Just after Google ai Center
Efficient Intelligence Center
What's wrong
Whats wrong with China in doing the first
2018a
Six months later
Google has decided not to renew this contract
Of artificial Intelligence project maven
15 March 2017
For Department of defense program
October
2018a
Google product
Other warning of data
The massive defense Department of applied computing contract
Potentially What time Being
US dollar
因為要給你
Champion US dollar
I will not see you
Because you are the Department of defense of America
They don't Fit on surfaces with Chinese Hospital in
Let's talk talk about financial Center
In the Financial sector
0more m660
Enterprises in you are you are the capital market today
Where are Chinese
ABC
New York Stock exchange
Ck2 in acid
No.500
Over-the-counter Market
Which there is regulated and most popular for those seeking to school
Transparency and storage requirements
Manufacturing companies
哦
Heritrix background
It is not
Palace of mirrors
Dollars
It is 100 doors
From 180d to two hundred Million
American investors
A supporting The National Security abusers as well as human rights abuses
聊啥
Look at california example
聯盟
Researches
Investment officer
Off the california
Public employees retirement
System
California prs
Calpers
Chalmers is One of the country's largest pension funds
Amenities rm350壁燈
For public employee
River retired from or currently working here
Most
Most of the state and local public agencies in california
Chinese propaganda device
People's Daily
Hotels restaurants
Playlist
Allegiance
To his motherland
給我隨friend to the comments China
Mongoose for Android in comments China
I came to the genetics to study
At the University of california Davis n90 n95
Prior To his position and
Calpers
夢cf75
Investment officer at the State administration of foreign exchange of China estate
Warriors
City is a Chinese
Alexandria mistreated agency under the State council
Test
Reflecting the rules and regulations cover in foreign exchange Market activities
And manage risk of foreign exchange reserves
Just like fire
NBA
United States
This is held by The People's
Bank of China
Stood at more than 30 Million dollars and of December 2010
Tesla control Engineering
China's foreign reserves system is One of these institutions of the world's second-largest
你看了沒
Can imagine that have and not to financial officer 30 US government
Vertu
我姐夫
Trusted
17cm
Of America retirement portfolios
Archana securities
American people use your recommendation to support the Chinese comments policy
Arch enemy
Of America
This relationship
Google's
Both ways
Today is that investors forum
Seven steps in US for the longer
It is without
Visit at the same time
Open investment
The Nations or side of the united States
Internet Explorer environment
From University endowment to government
Pension funds
Institutional investors
Hacking challenge
To achieve this analysis
Rick owens
Solrj application to the US
Bond Market
Businessman community structure senior approaches to previous
Changing landscape
Unanimously increased risk in asset class investment Services emerging markets
A private equity
Pcman
Increase For Working at that include include Windows
Managed service
China in particular
XX
Attention
The sheer size of Us economy
There is a constant for future was especially against the memory
Office2008 Financial crisis
One China China
And only breitbart
In the world economic landscape
Makes China is perfect candidate
Fluorescence intensity factors with this eating the next chapter 4 Pro
為什麼我說investment Bank Search and goldman sachs JP Morgan
JPMorgan chase
Blackstone ETC
Old has significant investment in China
沒事沒事很快
Walmart boy
金條
Qualcomm
All my question in China
Large number of family members of two
Commonest
Keras
For these companies
AliExpress families with great wealth of social and investment
American Stock Market
認為類型
Anaconda3 vim
Cause the security
Future of united States
How does the united States get along with China
2.the prev
It is set to four years ago
Understand persisting 97th
The united States established
Diplomatic relations with companies China under the consideration
American China to restrain the soviet Union
It is understandable to show the letter of two tables
Android source
南亭的亭臺
天安門massacre happened
In the month
After
The crackdown
Then president George hw Bush
三w 27th St Lawrence Agriculture and White House securely And why
Weather channel brands struct to Beijing
Guarantee shopping on the Chinese communist party regimes Spirit
The Model of Tiananmen massacre
Latin America will maintain the relationship and you leave the contamination whether It's on the Surface to
American Express
Three years later
The united States turn on
Greenlight
Fort communist China to other than in the world Market
Poweramp
南慶南集數
The united States and common is China's China
The memorandum of understanding not commit China
Openappmkt
To united States
Export
因為2
United States is committed to supporting China's accession
To the world trade organization wto
Which began as three years running
Supply of united States
The nightmare of the middle class
Crossfit
Goose
Give my comments China
我要被稱為next
December the eleventh
2010chinajoy
Became a member of the world trade organization
Americans investment course in to China
Ntdchinese
Product manufacturing of Chinese people
Point americas
Market
Android Market
Investment out
Introduction
Miss America neighbor Being replaced
By Chinese leaves
American people
Pendant
American police
Halton Ocean Which has improved
2B disaster
小品comment China steel economic prosperity
The middle Class in China will grow will grow and translation of political institutions will have
United States
Has been sitting on Green Card
Components Which can use to have various
The manufacturer
Battlefield weapon
Destroyer
The essence of this story
You get one cannot customer
Weather is in ideologically against God
You cannot set
Weather is in office
Criminals Who tries
Vascular people and animals
When enjoying the Cheap orders from depth images in
You are planning the fundamental understanding of human beings
如圖K the costs are not only Chinese people but also American people
Even American president
From the nationwide unemployment
突出汗VS victims
From the community Class of the one belt
To the Outlet
Crisis
From fake News
Synthesis and other conservative media
The surprising president Trump tweets
What happened to us
Is gradually happening to you too
Look at the wires that began in Minneapolis as president of America
It is American version of the cultural revolution Which happens in China
In an interesting facts
Flowers
Running around the united States with billions of companies and ideology target
To be election of November
5k suspension system
United States have large scale ddos attack
Distributed distributed denial of service attack
字母表
Fortnite Instagram
Comcast introspect
Experienced
好姐姐
With the target
Business communication infrastructure
Next
The target will be read and electricity Power plant and infrastructure
Underwater
Attacks are from within and outside
Enemy is Chinese communist party Brazil
United States is only the sport in the world
That's it can flourish
United States
New World Class into the place
What would you do What do you do in response to the current situation
Call father
Rubber
Coffee
Call Apple
有
In recent years or on the next
Managers are representative
Concentrators
Instagram
Tom cotton
這個主屏
Texas Center North Hollywood
Others
I don't know
In this historical turning Point self-reflection is critical
We have identified as various really work on Which define
忽略二
INS
This historical turning point
The belief in God is vital
It is very visited a situation
People have deviation from gosport
Fasola
Another question
I have a belief system
What is my you are gone
I know we saw the nation and the institutions
Based on the block of Urban culture
Andrew Christian believe
People What about each other
Which you Which is going to happen
Unit is happening
We do not
Take What actions
I came to the next
Because I defended
The limits of human beings
I would like to live with you side by side
For our common future
I would like to Fly with you side by side
報告
Thank you
大不了什麼呀
Excuse me Could you please speak More slowly
OK
Nokia Nokia
微軟
NBA
Windows
生活動
Thank you Thank you
54運動
First we need to define for manufacture
Flex
If you're talking about
Eclipse的DNS sector to combat and together
Baby
We don't do we begin to the talking about
Black different Animals together
My words
Make various
Music
Indifferent receiver
Eve
Transistors on human beings
If we define Manager at this way
I would like to say this
River is manufacturer
Suppress the definition
IPad molecule monocle
Leveldb don't know the buttons in the
Endnote word kinematical level or in the intensity of urbanization
The first time
虎
Ubuntu NVIDIA drivers
Is not affected by
Professional manufacturer
3點
After-sales
With unknown reason
WeChat
Npm publish their
Sassicaia don't know the world is
Papers for years and after their Friends
Friends Nobel prize winner
Pointed out
混血兒
Amsterdam
Australian
End
Norwegian scientists pointed out
Nn including Russian
Receptive fields and various kinds of Labor
超seabird in Harvard University
Was arrested by Dr
阿爾
Unknown number got was arrested from the
Harvard and in Boston area
超libhiredis.a
Power of the higher
Fire and chemical department
Nfv
FBI
Disclose system is to
Is250 relationship between China comments and common previous
Payment
So-called 1000x first
Product
He is kind of the 1000x with
Horace
This is
What is the students
WhatsApp
His Academic background background
What she do is to use
皇城
Technology
出use some metamaterials with the brain
With spring
FC2
Different
Reporters for these variables in Wuhan
武漢
Chinese
Kuantan
Biological
Technologies大
Trained by transfer
Asp.net are you Can Google Google Scholar
愛
Yes I appreciate the president Trump held in China this way but I hope
President Trump
Trade China tower
Regards
The trade deal with China
Very important thing but I don't think China will always do in the future
I don't think we will do this
My thinking on the Customer and other guys in in
China
Mikrotik set the biological technology
Advance in united States
What's
River has been to China
我想去找水果China
What
出門傳聞
Passport
我跟happiest harvesting and Lost River
勞動部門
房東partitions
並use after effects
胸悶
彩虹
Bootstrap
The spread of this kind of wires
鬧事
People's lives are touch
List of buyers
Stride rite
Baby
Quantum materials
有什麼事
Powerball
Carrier of list
Virus
Nih National institutes of Health
Find
With people who have Library
就2000cc
坐Cruise
看看這樣
Friends
US government
笑臉expert to investigate
武漢
MD Anderson
What time is it
Extends to What extent US government involved in the
Development
Vc2010
Android MP4
Minecraft
United Nations
I have a question
Yes
President Trump
Send messages to
退出
出沒的model with our music you understand their
就是說處
We will we will we
UC
Elementary school
Descriptions and small pieces
搜索Chinese
Coalesce
推力圓怎麼
Tunet
Private
Perfect
I think
Understand
Smartisan skill
In this place for kids school
你叫什麼
Wireless
Purpose
Maybe we try to erase
Hong Kong
Forecasting with some people But we cannot
Seoul
Weaken the controller
University in China and letting go to
Christmas
允兒
人民
愛的天氣
Weather
Ireader
現在
Protect against
明天
然後
MC
晚安
I have a question I have an answer but I don't know if my answers will satisfy you
I have experienced a very difficult
Situation in my life
Max3232
Important
One is self-reflection
肖perfection
Really Who I Am
What kind of metals
Is to find myself
Color
Is he living God
I think that as a student is very important
One is two
Traffic is connected to your self
Rather is
Kinect2
海爾濱
After do not Every body will find it
The rise of a great War
一無二肖
If the opportunities will
Appear
一Windows
Don't care
You can India
America
To wait for the opportunity
這片vanderbilt University of
如何
杯子
Christmas
I have some flowers
Learn about the quantum programming practicing
Amplifiers包
出門兒跟Harvest
Happened in China
If you are interested in I will
Payoneer
Vpn